[theme music playing]
[man] Congressman, a group of bandits
robbed the gambling den.
We lost about 100,000 pesos.
[Julio] I'm putting up
a 100,000-peso reward
for every bandit they catch.
Dead or alive.
[Fernan] We have the same goal,
but different perspectives.
I just hope we can work together
to fight against the Ardientes.
[reporter] Is there any truth
to the allegations against you?
You shameless thieves!
[Emilia screaming] Hey! Ouch!
Whoever's spreading rumors
about our family, come out!
[Ivy] This is only the beginning
of our battle against the Ardientes.
And I promise you,
the Ardientes are going down, Mom.
She's not the only one behind this.
Someone big is backing her up.
[Claire] Who could that be?
[Emilia] Could it be her darned daughter?
Do you know whom I'm suspecting?
Miss Aguas.
You don't deserve to be
called "Congressman".
You are a dirty politician,
and I will bring you down.
You can't buy me.
[Julio] Julio Ardiente's wrath…
-is like a hurricane.
-No!
It will destroy everything in its path.
[Ivy] Suicide?!
Who does that congressman
think he's fooling?!
I'm sure he had her killed!
[Diego] I'm sure Ivy's case will
be compromised because of this.
I need to help her.
Where's Camia Cruz?
We want to hear her story.
Is someone protecting her?
We need a statement on this, Attorney.
What is she afraid of?
Ivy, you can trust me. I'll help you.
Even if I have to testify
against the family
who raised me, I'll do it.
He's right, Ivy.
We need all the help that we can get now.
I spoke to the judge earlier,
and he's inclined to dismiss the case
if Camia won't show up in court.
It's time for me to face them--
If you're going to face them, I will too.
[Julio] We are celebrating my victory.
This case will be dismissed
without Camia Cruz in the picture.
We're having a grand press conference
for Papa tomorrow.
So, I want you to come with me.
Mom. I know where you're going
to make your big reveal.
-I like that smile, Emilia.
-Smile of success, Aunt Claire.
[Emilia] That press conference
will bury him into the ground.
He's in for a big surprise.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Back then,
I used to dress you up…
and get you ready
for important events like this.
Honestly, Mom, I still feel nervous.
Don't be, Lily.
You're much stronger
than you think you are.
In the 13 years that we were separated,
you proved that you are a strong woman.
That you're ready for this battle.
Come here.
I'm proud of you, Lily.
Your father and I.
So don't worry.
I know…
justice is on our side.
I can't wait to reveal myself
to the Ardientes.
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
♪ Let her cry ♪
♪ For she's a lady ♪
♪ Let her dream… ♪
[Filipino folk song playing]
[Filipino folk song continues playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Ivy!
-Emilia!
Hi!
Papa.
-Yes?
-Look who's here!
Good evening, Miss Aguas.
Long time, no see!
Indeed, Congressman. Long time, no see!
I missed you!
That's why I accepted Emilia's invitation.
I didn't want to miss this event.
Really, now?
You know, I was under the impression…
you were hiding from me
because you did something wrong.
I did something wrong?
Tell me.
I don't think this is the venue for that.
Congressman, you don't need a
proper venue to tell the truth.
Is it because I'm one of your suspects
behind the attacks against you?
[laughs]
Congressman, I'm not a fool to do that.
Because I invested a lot in your family.
And to be honest, I went away because
I didn't want to be involved
in your family's issues.
But now that you're going
to clear your name,
I guess there won't be any more problems.
So, shall we go in?
-Yes.
-Papa, we'll go in. Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[Filipino folk song playing]
[applause]
Good evening to everyone!
[host] Friends, let's all
welcome the Ardiente family!
-[applause]
-[entrance music playing]
[applause]
-[applause]
-[entrance music continues]
[host] Let's give our beloved congressman
a warm round of applause.
Congressman Julio Ardiente!
[applause]
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Please take your seats.
Sit down, please.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
To my children of the fourth district.
Thank you for coming
to this press event tonight…
which we deliberately organized…
to clarify all the accusations
against me and my family.
First of all, I would like to address…
the controversy about a woman…
named Camia Cruz.
[tense music playing]
-Papa.
-Yes, Emilia?
Can I speak about her?
By all means, go ahead.
Camia Cruz is furious at me,
so I should be the one
to clarify this issue.
Camia Cruz is nothing
but a desperate woman.
She once seduced my husband, Raul.
And as a woman, I fought for my marriage.
But now, she's back to get what is mine.
And she's spinning all these
lies against my family…
to destroy me.
You know, Camia Cruz,
if you're telling the truth…
then where are you?
Why are you hiding?
Come out! Show yourself!
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
Are you looking for me, Emilia?
Hello, Emilia.
Did you miss me?
And to the rest of the Ardiente family,
did you miss me too?
Yes! I am Camia!
And to everyone here… Can you hear me?!
I am Camia Cruz!
Well, Emilia?
Cat got your tongue?
Do you want me to pull it out for you?
Or would you prefer this?
Well, Emilia…
[chuckles]
Are you stressed?
I'm not a desperate woman!
I never stole anyone's husband!
The truth is,
you had my whole family killed!
How dare you!
-Let go of me!
-That's enough.
Jasmin? Camia?
You're alive?
Guards! Guards!
[Emilia] Get her out of here!
-She's not even invited!
-Wait.
Who's desperate now, Emilia?
Are you scared that I'll expose
all your secrets?
Wait! Wait! Drop your guns!
Drop them! Put them down!
You dared me to show up.
So, that's what I did.
Now that I'm here, your tails
are between your legs!
These murderers tried to silence me once.
But that won't happen again.
Because I will reveal the truth.
Is it true they killed
your husband and daughter?
What was their motive
for murdering your family?
Why did you only show up now?
Ma'am, please.
We need your testimony
against the Ardientes.
Don't come back here again, boy.
I don't want the Ardientes
knocking on my door too.
But they killed your husband!
Don't you want to avenge his death?
You don't understand, boy.
Here, the Ardientes are the law!
And anyone who opposes them
will end up six feet under.
Especially that Camia Cruz!
So, please, just leave me alone!
Ma'am, please I'm begging you.
Please help us help you.
I don't need your help!
Go away! Get out!
[Camia] My husband Dante was a lawyer.
We moved here to Poblacion Ardiente
because he was assigned here.
While working for the attorney's office,
Dante discovered all the
Ardientes' dirty secrets!
This province never had a zero crime rate!
Everywhere, there are people
being silenced or killed!
And the Ardientes are the ones behind it!
The attorney's office
was a front for them
to conceal their crimes!
[thumps cane]
Bravo!
[Julio] Wonderful!
Such a well-written speech!
You delivered it well too.
But this will all remain
to be a narrative.
There's no truth behind
this woman's allegations.
You're grasping at straws
that aren't there.
I can prove everything I've said.
[Julio] Prove what?!
That my political rivals paid
your husband to ruin my image?
Dante Cruz was an honest public servant!
Oh, shut up!
Are you sure about that?
[Emilia] Your husband went to
my office a couple of times.
He would fabricating
allegations against me…
so he could extort money from me.
You know, it hurts to admit this,
but I want everyone to know that…
you ruined my marriage!
That woman ruined my marriage!
Weren't you Diego's tutor?
But instead of teaching my son,
you stole my husband!
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Nanny?
-Hello, Diego?
Lily's mother, Miss Camia…
finally showed herself.
She's on TV. She's confronting
your mother and grandfather.
It's scary!
Why? What did they do to her?!
They humiliated her.
Your mother called her a mistress.
They're saying that she agreed
to be your tutor then…
because she wanted to seduce Raul.
They're all liars!
I'll go to the press conference.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
-Be careful, Diego.
-I will.
I stole your husband?!
Why don't we let Raul
tell us what really happened?!
Is your wife
telling the truth, Mr. Torillo?
No! He is not going
to give any statements now!
[scoffs] See that?
You're such a liar, Emilia!
The truth is…
your husband attempted to rape me!
Dante wanted to bring him to
justice, so you had him killed!
You poisoned him!
But that's not all!
You ordered to have me
and my daughter killed!
But the time has come…
for justice to be served.
It's time for you to pay
for what you've done
to the people of Poblacion Ardiente!
I swear…
After this…
no Ardiente will ever hurt
or abuse anyone again!
[Julio] Well, well, well…
It looks like…
this press conference
has turned into a witch-hunt!
It's her word against ours.
It's best for us to end
this party early tonight.
This will only lead to gossiping…
while nothing this woman
has said is proven.
Everything that comes out of her mouth…
can't really be trusted.
[tense music swelling]
I'll see you in court…
Camia Cruz.
To all of you, thank you for accepting
the invitation of the Ardientes.
[Emilia] Raul, let's go.
Raul!
Let's go!
[tense music continues playing]
-Congressman!
-Congressman.
Congressman!
Is it true that ex-governor
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo
had Camia Cruz's family killed?
Everything Miss Camia Cruz says is a lie.
They're all fabricated lies to destroy me…
to destroy my name, to destroy our family.
Come now, you know us.
You know the Ardientes.
For so many years, we have
served the public faithfully.
You've followed our career.
You know that we have
an excellent track record
when it comes to public service.
Based on that,
you'll see that we're honest and sincere.
That's why I'm not worried or afraid
of Miss Cruz's threats.
I know that in court,
all her charges against
us will be proven false.
The Ardiente family…
will continue to serve the people.
Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
Now, if you'll excuse us…
Thank you, Congressman.
-Thank you too.
-What do you plan on doing next?
[Julio] Well, it all depends on Miss Camia
and how she plans
on disturbing our family.
Then, we will just reciprocate.
[reporter] So, what will be
your next move, Miss Cruz?
The Ardientes are very influential people.
How will this affect
your position in court?
The Ardientes might be influential,
but I'm not backing down from the case.
[Camia] I believe that
the truth will prevail
against their power.
You mentioned your husband
and daughter were murdered.
Isn't it hard to fight this battle alone?
My daughter is always with me.
She's in my heart.
Thank you for listening
to my story. Excuse me.
Wait, Auntie. Where's Raul?
I don't know. He was with us just before.
Could he be…
Okay, I know where he is.
Emilia, wait. Madrigal, go with her.
[exhales sharply]
[Raul clears throat]
Camia, can I-- Wait.
I just want to--
Camia, I wanna talk to you.
-Let go of me!
-It's okay. Let him go.
What do you want, Raul?
Why did you come here, Camia?
You know what they'll do to you.
They'll have you killed.
Raul, I won't hide like a coward.
You'll all pay for this!
[Camia] You kept me locked up
for so long, Raul.
You imprisoned me! And for what?
So you wouldn't have to face
the sins you've committed?!
[quietly] Lily… stay here.
[Raul] They left you to die, Camia.
But I didn't. I saved you.
I saved your life, Camia.
Raul!
[Camia] Locking me up all those
years wasn't "saving" me.
You're no different from the Ardientes!
You're the root of all
my family's misfortunes!
You robbed me of my life!
What can I do to earn
your forgiveness, Camia?
I will never forgive you, Raul!
Hey, you skank! Well?
-Well?!
-Emilia, stop it.
-Raul…
-Stop it!
What? Why are you stopping me?
-Leave us alone.
-You're taking her side?!
You bastard! You two disgust me!
Don't you realize that
this woman will send us to jail?
And this woman will destroy us all!
Do you realize that?!
Yes, I know.
We'll all rot together in hell.
Well, I'm glad you got
yourself a one-way ticket.
And you, Camia Cruz…
Listen to me. You'll regret crossing me!
I'll make you regret ever being born!
-Let's go. Let's go.
-You worthless bastards!
[Emilia] Let's go!
Let's go, Dad.
[Julio] Damn! Damn!
Damn that woman.
Papa, let's stop this.
We shouldn't be the ones fighting.
We have to be united against Camia.
You're right. I agree.
But on one condition.
Okay, Papa. Tell me anything. I'll do it.
Get rid of Raul!
I'm telling you. He's a threat!
He might just betray us.
I understand, Papa. I'll take care of him.
Finally! My daughter is back!
-This is all my fault.
-Yes, Dad. It is.
Mrs. Camia was right.
What you did was unforgivable.
Do you hate me now too, Diego?
I don't know, Dad.
But one thing's for sure.
I don't trust you anymore.
I understand.
I promise you this…
I'll change for the better.
I'll earn back your trust in me.
I hope so, Dad.
But don't just promise.
Do it.
I hope you mean what you say.
What's wrong with you, Arnaldo?
I noticed you've been deep in thought.
For some time now.
I'm just trying to figure out
your next move, Grandpa.
I was wondering if I'd make the same move
if I were in your situation.
[laughs]
You know what?
There's no such thing
as the absolute right move.
What matters is…
you cling to the absolute truth
when it comes to the Ardiente family,
which is…
nobody can ever bring us down.
As for Camia Cruz? [scoffs]
She's nothing without those
witnesses she's been hiding.
And I know you're trying
your best to find them.
Definitely.
I swear I'll find where they're hiding.
And I believe you.
And now, we can have a good night's sleep.
Just think of Camia…
as a nightmare.
You're doing very well, Arnaldo.
Take your rest.
Okay. Good night.
Good night.
All those who oppose me…
will be silenced.
Especially you, Camia Cruz.
No one can bring the Ardientes down…
as long as I'm alive.
[instrumental theme music playing]
[Ivy] Mom, you'll be staying here for now.
But Lily, why can't I stay
in your rest house?
You can't.
The rest house is under my name.
It's too dangerous for you to stay there.
But…
Can you sleep here tonight?
Mom, I want to, but…
I need to go home to my
house here in Ardiente.
I don't want our enemies
getting suspicious.
I understand.
But be careful over there.
I will, Mom. You too.
Your bodyguards will stay with you.
And I'll always check on you.
-Goodnight, Mom. I love you.
-I love you. Good night.
Let's just call each other.
[Ivy] All right. You should get some rest.
Raul, I'm giving you one last chance.
If you pull that stunt again,
I will kill you myself.
I'd much rather see you dead
than see you end up with Camia.
I don't care.
Oh, really now?
What if I have her killed again?
Just so you know,
Papa told me to get rid of you.
But because I love you,
I'm giving you one last chance.
So don't try to betray me.
Understand?
They're going to arraign
our case against the Ardientes.
And they'll definitely plead not guilty.
We need to be ready for the trial.
We will study everyone's testimony
to make sure nobody makes any mistakes.
What will happen to us
after the case, Attorney?
Yeah. And what happens if we lose?
Will they still protect us?
Of course. I will protect you.
And the Ardientes won't defeat us…
because the truth is on our side. Right?
-But they can still twist it.
-If you let them.
If you let yourselves become cowards.
Remember this…
we are all victims of the Ardientes.
They used all of you…
to carry out their evil plans.
Now, it's time to right your wrongs.
She's right. We need to trust her.
She'll protect us and our families.
Justice will finally be served
for my sister's death…
and the murders
of all those innocent people.
The Ardientes will
finally be brought down.
Which is why…
we will all work together
to bring down the Ardientes.
Understood?
Attorney, it's not safe here.
We need to move them all
to the safe house.
[knocking on door]
[secretary] Mayor, these are
from the social welfare office.
These are the documents you asked for.
Just leave them there.
And take these signed documents.
Thank you, sir.
Um, Mayor, what are those
files from DSWD for?
Why are you asking
so many questions? Get out.
I'm sorry. I'm just concerned about you,
especially after what I watched on TV.
I don't want you to lose your position
because I might lose my job too.
You'll lose your job if you
don't get out of my sight.
I'm sorry.
[sinister music playing]
I'm okay, Mom. I just went home…
to get a few things.
I'll leave here right away.
[Edward] Be careful, Maria.
Text us as soon as you get
back to your aunt's house.
And don't go out, okay?
They already sent some men
over to keep you safe.
Okay, Mom.
Okay.
Esther, Edward… Are you okay?
Is there a problem?
No. We just checked on our daughter.
-That's right.
-She seems fine.
She just dropped by our house
to get some things.
But she said she'll go back
to her aunt straight away.
That's good to hear.
You need to go. They're waiting for you.
Okay. Let's go, Edward.
[ominous music playing]
-[muffled screams]
-[man grunts]
[muffled screams]
Okay. Bring her inside.
[goon] Hurry. Get in.
Here you go, dear.
I missed cooking for you.
It's your favorite!
Thank you, Mom.
Lily.
Is there something bothering you?
I'm just thinking about…
our witnesses.
They've sacrificed a lot
for their families too.
That's why…
I'm more determined
to bring the Ardientes down.
Especially now that…
we have everything we
need to present in court.
The Ardientes won't stand a chance.
[Julio] Make sure that
everyone who's important…
will be there tonight.
-Yes, Congressman.
-That'll be all. You can go.
Hey, Arnaldo.
[Julio chuckles]
What's with that smile on your face?
Does this mean that you've found
what you were looking for?
Yes. I know where they are.
Make sure that…
each and every one of those witnesses…
regrets their decision to
go up against the Ardientes.
I want each of them to suffer.
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Dad?
-Hello…
Diego. I'm glad you picked up.
What is it?
Do you know how to get
in touch with Camia?
Dad, can you please stop it?
Listen to me, Diego.
Your grandfather already
knows where Camia's hiding
the witnesses against the Ardientes.
You should tell Camia.
Okay, Dad. Leave it to me.
[Emilia] Ivy, I'm so glad that
you're back in Ardiente.
I finally have someone
to confide my problems to.
Not just yet. Because, I
won't be staying here long.
-Sit down, Emilia.
-Thank you.
I need to oversee my
other businesses in Manila.
Besides…
Congressman and I
aren't on good terms yet.
So, I'm a little worried that…
he might have me killed.
Hey, I'd like to apologize
about the press conference.
I hope it doesn't ruin our relationship.
You know, that fiasco thing?
Well, I understand. I need to understand.
You're facing a huge problem, Emilia.
I bet it's giving you a headache.
[sighs]
Well, the only person giving us
a headache is that Camia.
But, you know…
I believe that all headaches can be cured.
Really?
Are you sure that Camia
is just a headache?
Isn't Camia Cruz somewhat…
like a cancer,
who is out to kill the Ardientes?
[Emilia scoffs]
Ivy, there's a solution
to every problem, right?
Especially now that Papa
and I have patched things up.
You've patched things up with your father?
-Yes, Ivy.
-I'm happy for you.
At… At least.
I know. That's why
I've decided to postpone
all my plans against him.
What's important now is that we're united…
in our battle against Camia.
Hey, I hate to do this.
But I have to go, Ivy.
You know that I'm very busy.
Thank you for your time.
[chuckles] Leaving so soon?
What are you so busy with?
We didn't even have time
to drink wine or--
Well, next time, Ivy.
Thank you again for your time.
I really hope you win
the case against Camia.
It would make me so sad to see you…
go to jail, Emilia.
Thank you for your concern, Ivy.
I have to go. Bye.
Hey! What's he doing here?
[Ivy] Oh.
Diego called me earlier to tell me
that there's something we need
to discuss about the farmers.
Something to consult me about.
Well, I told him that it wouldn't hurt
if I listen to him. Right?
Okay. I'll get going. Bye again.
-Bye, Emilia.
-Bye.
Diego, what are you doing here?
Ivy…
The Ardientes already know where
you're hiding the witnesses.
[Julio] Don't worry.
This issue will all be over soon.
Right now, our lawyers are looking into
how they can shut that Camia Cruz up.
But, in the meantime,
let's just work for the people.
Congressman, our friends
from the press are inviting you
for an exclusive interview.
Will you accept the invite?
Why not?
I'll tell my staff to call them up
so we can schedule an interview
as soon as possible.
[chuckles]
I admire your confidence, Congressman.
This issue will be put to rest
sooner than expected.
You bet, Governor.
To the congressman.
-To the congressman.
-Okay!
Are you sure, Diego? How is that possible?
And where did you get that information?
My dad told me.
[scoffs]
Your father told you?
Well, I don't trust your father.
You know that, right, Diego?
And if you'll keep believing him…
Diego, I'm sorry,
but maybe I shouldn't trust you either.
I understand how you feel, Ivy.
But it wouldn't hurt to take precautions.
[dramatic music playing]
Mayor,
have you found a way
to silence that woman?
What's it to you?
Your assignment is
to look after my mother.
[Raul] I can help Camia more if
I stay here with the Ardientes.
You traitor!
I will find out who you're working with!
[Arnaldo] Answer me when I'm asking you!
Where is your safe house? [cocks gun]
-Sir, don't! No!
-No, Sir! No!
Esther and Edward…
-are in danger.
-[gunshots]
[Ivy] All our witnesses need to transfer
to another safe house.
I need to go there now.
[theme music playing]